I just caught my biggest
trade of the month I've never seen this happen ever
so I was in this trade I was on the stream
this morning I said alright guys I'm gonna buy it here
at one dollar and twenty cents at a simple
pullback off of VWAP and I said well I'm just gonna look for the break of the high of the day
well it squeezes it in less than five seconds
to three dollars and ninety seven cents that's not a glitch
that actually happened 1:20
to 3 97 in literally like two seconds
look at the 10 second chart this actually happened 1:20
to 3:97 I got nothing sold
because I thought it was a glitch and I said well there's no way this is actually happening
so I ended up trading myself
from 1:20 all the way to two dollars and fifty cents
this is one of those times where I was completely lost for words no
idea what it just happened I thought it was fake
people were up five grand in seconds 21R day in seconds absolutely
unbelievable
this is why whenever the opportunity is there you take your shot
and over time you'll catch a big home run